♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday AD ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ When the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
- Let's go.
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
Hi, girl.
♪ Tom Servo ♪
What a cool guy.
♪ Crow ♪
Oh, wise cracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself ♪
♪ It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors whirring)
- Hey, everybody.
My name is Joel, I'm marooned
up here in outer space.
I'm all alone expect
for the companionship
of my two robot friends that I,
are of my own design.
There are two evil
overlord scientists
that are sending me
horrendous films,
but I can handle it
because I'm a hu-man.
Two, three.
(blues harmonica)
♪ Hey there you people ♪
♪ In front of your TVs ♪
♪ Sitting along that line ♪
♪ I'll be back ♪
♪ From the commercial ♪
♪ In a few minutes time ♪
- [Electronic Voice]
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two.
Commercial sign now.
♪ Aint that a hu-man ♪
(blues harmonica)
(upbeat music)
♪ H-u-m-a-n ♪
♪ A human ♪
♪ Human ♪
♪ Hu ♪
- Cheese it, you guys.
Get rid of the harps,
it's the overlords.
- Good day, my Muddy
Waters wannabe.
- Hey, sirs.
How's everything on Earth?
- How would we know?
We've been subterranean for,
93 days.
We're as abstracted
from reality as you are.
Maybe more.
- Geeze, don't say hi.
Well, is it time for
the invention exchange?
- Is it time for the
invention exchange?
Yes, show us what
you've got, pig boy.
- Well, you know
how it is on Earth
when, you know they have
those giant enclosed stadiums
and you can't smoke in it
and I always thought
it was kind of peculiar
because you drive giant,
hell belching monster trucks
but you can't smoke, right?
- Yeah, yeah right.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, so I
invented this thing.
It's a thing for smokers
and it's a monster truck.
I call it the nitro
burning funny pipe.
Okay, and I just
(engine revving)
start it up here.
(engine roaring)
Okay, and then I
light a match here.
- Ow.
- Sunday, Sunday, Sunday
will see Joel's lung turn
into a giant tar pit.
- Wow, that's real
gear crushing,
tire popping tobacco
satisfaction.
- Oh yes, very nice.
Although, we don't smoke.
Well, here's our, Joely Ace.
As you know, face mask
throughout history
left the bank robber, or thug,
completely expressionless.
Well, we've taken care of that.
Larry.
- We've invented the
stocking mask of the future
with articulated eyebrows.
- Yes, no longer will
a desperate criminal
go misunderstood.
The SM of F takes care
of that completely.
The demo, Larry.
- All right, put $10,000
in the bag, unmarked bills,
right now.
Hey, ladies.
Oh, it works, cool.
All right, see, you
touch that alarm button,
I'm gonna have to
rip off your fingers
and you're gonna
have to reattach them
at the nearest hospital
with laser surgery.
It's really cool
how they do that.
They--
- Larry.
- Sorry.
I know what you're thinking,
you're thinking did I use
six bullets, or only five?
See in all the excitement,
I don't know myself.
I saw it in a movie,
it's really good.
Clint.
- Oh yes, well, that's our
experiment this week, Joel.
Now, the movie is a greasy
little sci-fi number
called Robot Holocaust
and it's in color.
- [All] Yay!
- But it's edited
for television.
- [All] Boo.
- Fruits you must
never enjoy, Jolene.
- But there's more.
- I know, Commando Cody, right?
- Exactly.
Deal with it, smart boy.
- Enjoy.
(alarm blaring)
- We got movie sign!
(tense orchestral music)
- [Joel] No, I was
saying they used servos
to move those eyebrows.
- [Servo] Sunday Sunday Sunday.
- [Crow] Yours was cool, Joel.
- [Joel] Thanks.
- Hey, is that his high
school yearbook picture?
- [Joel] I don't know.
(triumphant orchestral music)
- There's a bunch
of rocks ahead.
That will give us some shelter.
- He's heading for some rocks.
We'll have to stop him.
- [Servo] They must
read the script.
(tense orchestral music)
- That's our B pressure line.
We're stuck.
- I'll say we are.
Pressures down to nothing.
- I could fix this,
if I have time.
- [Joel] And if I knew how.
- Try to stop them
with your grenades.
- Okay.
- They stopped behind a rock.
- [Joel] Which one
of us is talking?
- But I think I can blast them.
(tense orchestral music)
- [Servo] Go.
Right in the plywood.
- [Joel] Now, I'm just
gonna drop my spleen on 'em.
- What was that?
- Sounded like a spleen.
By this time, my lungs
were aching for air.
- [Servo] If the
tanks a rocking,
don't come a knocking.
- [Joel] Huh?
Oh great, he's drunk
again on rye whiskey.
- We're stuck.
- So is the other car.
Let's go after him
with our A pistols.
(tense orchestral music)
- Whoa, he's got the
Zackleys big time.
- Did you stop them?
- For a little while
but I don't know for how long.
- [Joel] Dad, I can't keep
covering for you at the office.
- Pressure line.
- Okay.
(tense orchestral music)
- [Servo] Guys, over here.
Whoa.
- Taste my steel, jughead.
(explosion)
- [Joel] Yikes.
- [Servo] That's not fair
to play catch like that.
(explosion)
- [Joel] Oh for
the love of Mike.
(man shouting)
Come in here and
quit horsing around.
- [Crow] Come on, mom,
just one more grenade.
- [Joel] Just one more.
- [Servo] Little lead
sandwich for ya, moon geek.
(tense orchestral music)
- No, D for drive, Ted.
- [Servo] Shrapnel
on your brain?
(tense orchestral music)
- [Joel] Jimmy cracked
corn and I don't care.
- [All] Jimmy cracked
Jimmy cracked corn
and I don't care
the masters gone away.
- [Servo] Those
things shut off quick.
- Yeah, you don't get
run on on the moon.
- [Servo] Well,
expect for this movie.
It just runs on and on.
- [Crow] True.
- [Joel] Ted, we can't bring
your puppet everywhere.
- Put this aboard.
- [Servo] Jimmy likes
to travel, Cody.
- I'll ditch this car.
- Right.
- Oh where you gonna
ditch a high gloss
plywood moon vehicle?
- [Servo] Besides, we
don't call them ditches
on the moon, we
call them craters.
- Mmm, peaceful.
- Meanwhile, back
at the slag heap.
- Okay, we're ready.
- Right.
- [Joel] Ready for what?
- Are you going to let
me go before you leave?
- No, we're taking you with us
and you better go
back to your quarters
until we get started.
Get going!
- [Joel] Take off
that stupid hat.
- [Servo] Cody, don't wear
your jet pack In the house.
What if that thing went off?
- Safety belts fastened?
- [Joel] They haven't
been invented yet, though.
- Cool.
- [Servo] Moon man flambe.
- Ron Howard pops the clutch
and tells the moon
to eat my dust.
(tense orchestral music)
- [Servo] What happened?
- Hey.
- [Joel] Film broke?
- Oh.
- [All] Boo.
- [Joel] That's no good.
I'm gonna go back and check.
Let's see here.
I know its...
(goofy muzak)
Let's see here.
- Hey.
- [Servo] Is it Cambot, Joel
- [Joel] I don't know.
I can't tell.
(upbeat music)
(eerie tense music)
Hey, you guys, I
think I got it going.
- [Servo] Cool.
- [Joel] Yeah, it's working.
- [Crow] Great.
- [Servo] It really is
in color, too, look.
- Just in time.
- [Narrator] The last
city still stood.
The remaining home
of what was left
of the civilization
of New Terra.
- [All] Pittsburgh.
(soft tense music)
- [Narrator] The society
had been all but destroyed
by the robot rebellion of '33.
- [Joel] Oh, my hips
still hurts from that one.
Cyborg blind sided me.
- hey look, it's Aaron
Spelling's house.
- [Servo] Boy, that place
sure isn't up to code.
- [Joel] It's Three
Rivers stadium.
- [Narrator] Chaos had
lead to a radiation spill
far more deadly that
any nuclear warfare.
- [Servo] They
barbecued in parks
with strict fire codes.
- [Narrator] The world had
been brought to it's knees
by the Robot Holocaust.
- [Servo] By the title.
(tense music)
- Robert Culf's smarter brother.
- [Joel] Nadine Hart
of Rogers and Hart.
Look at me, I'm a turtle.
- [Servo] Is that you, Joel?
- [Joel] No, that's
the other Joel.
There's two of us.
- Jennifer Delora.
She's a Delorean.
(Crow chuckling weakly)
- [Servo] Andrew How-arth?
- Fine, how arth you?
- [Servo] Classic.
- Good one.
- Ba-bing.
- [Joel] Angelika Jager,
she's playing the
big lipped woman.
Barry Zetlin.
(goofy laughing)
Hello there.
- [Servo] Cynthia DePaula.
Good school, great
basketball team.
- Tim Kincaid, Ruben
Kincaid's smarter brother.
- [Servo] A parking
ramp in Cincinnati.
- [Joel] I think it looks
more like a roller coaster
like Six Flags over Armageddon.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Armageddon
tired of this already.
- Hey, I bet those
guys are fighting
over the last corn
dog in existence.
(grunting)
- [Servo] What
happened to his butt?
Isn't there a salve for that?
- [Joel] You got a little huh.
- Yeah.
- A little something
on your mouth there, wipe that.
- [Joel] Get up, get up.
That's good.
You got to want it.
- I hate fights.
They're so smoky and noisy.
- [Joel] I'm editing this.
Huh?
Uh, inspected by number 12.
- Hey, couldn't he get arrested
for pulling that tag off?
- [Joel] Only if he
was wearing a mattress.
Looks like the sad
future of the WWF.
- [Servo] Look at
this Robo pick pocket.
- Nice tag.
(grunting)
- [Narrator] The remaining
citizens of New Terra
are known as Airslaves.
As far as they know,
the only other
inhabitants of the planet
who remain are the...
- [Joel] Love me.
Love me.
- [Narrator] Evil being who
controls the very atmosphere
that sustains them.
- [Servo] 'Cause as we
all know, to err is human.
- [Narrator] Stories of nomads
who roam the wastelands beyond
the outskirts of the city.
Outlaws, loners.
A legendary breed who
have somehow acclimated
to the poisonous air.
- [Servo] Actors,
lawyers, hot dog vendors.
Oh god, I need this job.
- Hey, am I my resume?
Where's Bobby Heenan
when you need him?
- [Servo] I wonder
what would happen
if there was card shares
after the apocalypse.
- [Neo Voiceover] If you
wish to be reactivated,
you will tell me what
takes place below.
- [Joel] Below what?
- [Neo Voiceover] I will give
you a five second activation
to respond.
- [Klyton] Please, master.
I am sorry for
trying to steal...
- [Crow] Why the long face?
- [Klyton] I am at your service.
- [Neo Voiceover] You
have three seconds.
- [Klyton] A contest, master.
- [Servo] They're
ventriloquisting each other.
- [Klyton] A fight to the death.
Each month the Dark
Ones sends a transbot
to each work
encampment in the city
to pick the two strongest
Airslaves against one another.
- [Neo Voiceover] The Dark One?
- [Klyton] The ruler
of all air space.
- [Joel] Arsenio?
- [Klyton] Their labor
fuels the power station.
Their station cleanses
the atmosphere
so that workers can continue
to fuel the power station.
- [Neo Voiceover] And you?
- [Klyton] I am but a
poor free bot, master.
- [All] Freebot!
Play freebot!
- [Klyton] My only
source of revenue.
I steal what I
can from who I can
in order to pay for the
upkeep of my mechanical parts.
- [Servo] Mechanical pot?
Is that a drug reference?
- [Joel] I don't think so.
You know, this movies
no Rocky, you guys.
- [Servo] Thank goodness.
- [Neo Voiceover] Reason
for these contests?
- [Klyton] The two
most powerful Airslaves
must fight till
one of them dies.
- [Crow] Or until they
capture the other's loincloth.
- [Klyton] To the power
station for his reward
but it is said that the
winner is actually destroyed.
- [Neo Voiceover] Destroyed?
- [Crow] Yes, destroyed.
Read my lips.
- [Klyton] In this way.
- [Crow] Or lip.
- [Klyton] The Dark One
can keep the Airslaves
from developing
leaders strong enough
to lead a rebellion.
- [Narrator] The power station.
- [Joel] Looks like they patched
into a Metallica
video, you guys.
- [Servo] I think
it's the maid .
And what a maid it is.
- Somethings wrong,
I can sense it.
- [Servo] Must be
cold in that room.
- [Dark One] Is it
the amphitheater?
- Yes, Dark One.
- Did she say stuffed one?
(crowd shouting)
- [Joel] I'm gonna die if
they start dancing cheek
to cheek all of a sudden.
- Do the dirty bump.
- [Servo] Look at that, it
looks like sneeze stalactites.
(crowd shouting)
- [Joel] I feel like I
could get in the middle
of this thing and
- Take 'em, Joel.
- [Torque] Kill him.
- No, he's our brother.
- [Servo] He aint heavy.
- [Torque] Kill him.
- Stop it.
This is not contest,
it is murder.
(mechanical whirring)
- [Servo] Well,
her corns are gone.
- [Torque] Interfere again.
- Hey, it's Miles Davis.
- [Torque] And I
will aim higher.
- [Joel] Well, it's good to
have goals, little crab guy.
- Weapons.
- We can get them.
(crowd shouting "No winner")
- [Joel] What are they
saying, no winter?
- [Servo] No dinner, I think.
- I don't think they want
Edgar Winter to play.
- [Servo] No acting, no acting.
- [Joel] Or Jonathan Winter.
(crowd shouting "No winner")
- [Crow] Tehran, 1979.
- [Crowd] No winner,
no winner, no winner.
No winner, no winner.
- [Servo] Peas and
carrots, peas and carrots.
- No liver?
- [Dark One] Valeria?
- Yes, Dark One?
- [Dark One] You
know what to do.
- [Joel] What, did
she say stock one?
Lock john?
(all coughing)
- [Servo] Oh, sore throat pain.
- [Joel] Is that George Bush?
(people coughing)
- Pretend you are
like the others.
- Father.
- Do as I say.
- [Joel] Fall down,
try to look realistic.
- Very nice.
- [Joel] Very uh...
- [Dark One] Who stands
against the forces
of the power station?
- Restore the atmosphere
and I will identify myself.
- Look out, he's
got an eggplant.
- [Dark One] Stay.
- Restore the atmosphere.
- [Dark One] Very well.
- [Servo] You dare
to test the power
of my dreaded eggplant?
- [Joel] Oh my
aching crowd scene.
(people coughing)
(whispering) Up
everybody, up, up.
Crowd.
- [Dark One] Did you
all have to be reminded
who was in control?
And what happens when the
Dark One is disobeyed?
- Pork one?
- One.
- [Dark One] He
will be attended to
but for the moment.
Torque, destroy the fighter.
- [Servo] Oh, what
a waste of an extra.
Oh.
You hate to see
him go like that.
- Take refuge in the
crowd and save yourself.
- No, my place.
- [Joel] Oh we better.
- [Servo] Take
refuge in the bridge.
- Won't always be
here to protect you.
Do it, now.
- Carry me.
- [Joel] No, walk yourself.
- It is you who need protection.
- Deeja, now.
(doors whirring)
♪ Peeking through the knothole ♪
- Stop, human.
You have entered the We Zone.
- A world that
revolves around us
and only us.
- All right, well
I was just going
to the galley to get
some food, you know,
and what do you want?
- No one crosses the We Zone
without doing
something for us first.
- Okay, what do
you want me to do?
- You must do the
disappearing coin trick.
- Yeah, good idea.
- All right, I can
do that for you.
You remember how it goes, right?
Start with an ordinary
quarter, right,
and then I start rubbing
it on my elbow, like that,
see that, Cambot?
Okay, and.
Oh, oh I didn't get
it to disappear yet.
Let's try it again.
I take the quarter and rub it
and it's gone.
- Hey, cool.
- Okay, can I go now?
- Now, you must walk
us on the ceiling.
- No, Crow, in character.
You must walk us on
the ceiling, human.
- You guys, you guys
know you're getting
way too big for that.
I can't walk you on the ceiling.
What else you want me to do?
- You must create a
severe weather condition
inside the satellite.
- Yeah.
- Like what?
- You know, the
Chinese snow trick.
- I can't do snow
storm in China.
It's in the shop, I'd
have to go get it.
What can I do that's real quick?
- Do goofus face for us.
- Yeah, crazy duck face.
- Okay.
I'll do it.
(goofy laughter)
- Oh, not the eyelids.
Oh, oh I hate that.
- All right, can I go now?
- Oh no, you must do for us
a hand stand.
- Yeah.
- Okay, if I do a
handstand can I go then?
- Oh, of course.
- All right sure,
let's try it here.
All right, ready?
Hand stand on the
count of three.
Three, two, one and oh.
- Oh, cool.
- [Joel] How's that, you guys?
- Shoes untied.
- Okay and down.
- Great handstand.
- There.
All right, I'm gonna
go the galley now.
You guys want anything?
- Yes, human.
Well, now that you mention it,
ravioli would be nice.
- Ravioli, okay.
- Yeah and uh,
I'd like a club sandwich
oh and could you
pull the extra bread
out of the middle?
I hate that.
- Okay, no problem,
I'll see you around.
- I love dinner theater.
- Yeah, you know it, pal.
(upbeat music)
- [Dark One] And now, old man.
- [Joel] All right,
all right, here we go.
- [Dark One] Who are you?
- I am a but a
simple man, Dark One.
A man who is clearly no
match for your powers.
- [Dark One] And yet you
breathe the poisoned air.
- I have no explanation.
- [Dark One] Perhaps a
visit to the power station
will loosen your tongue?
(Crow blowing raspberries)
Torque, take him.
- And no dinner.
- [Joel] Hey, she
didn't say anything.
- Who are you to keep
me from my father?
- Dave.
- [Klyton] His name is Neo.
He comes from the
wastelands beyond the city.
- You are immune to
the poisoned air?
- [Klyton] He can live anywhere.
On New Terra.
- Why must we
listen to a freebot
instead of the man himself?
- [Klyton] He speaks
to me telepathically.
- [Servo] Actually, it's
more tele-pathetic-ly.
- [Klyton] He's sure that
you will side with him.
- If he aims to
defeat the Dark One,
we stand with him.
- And you.
- My father is in danger,
what do you want of me?
- Just five minutes
of your time.
I know you haven't really
considered aluminum siding.
- Not effected.
- My father is a scientist.
(Crow and Servo grunting dumbly)
He has created a small device
which subverts the Dark
One's atmosphere control.
He only had time to
create one for himself
and me before he was taken away.
- [Joel] They're real expensive.
Oh, she's wearing a bell tone.
- [Crow] Ew, cooties.
- These work yards
used to house something
called subway system.
- [Servo] They used to be
in things called cities.
- Set up his shop in
one of these rooms.
Now that the device
has been perfected
he said that we could
all be fitted for one
within the next few days.
- They would work in
the wastelands as well?
- [All] Shut up.
- I have been sent here
by the Rebel society
from what you call
the wastelands.
We are organizing an army
to destroy the Dark One
and his forces at
the power station.
- [Klyton] Do you swear
you allegiance Nero?
- Hey, it's a young
Robin Williams
on right there right there.
- [Klyton] And rescue
your scientist.
- So your tribe is some
kind of hybrid race?
- [Joel] Yeah, you
could say that.
- You could say that.
Our number grows each day.
- [Joel] Thanks to me.
- Now that you know
of my father's device,
you need us as much
as we need you.
- And vice versa.
- We don't need the device.
You do.
But an army of Airslaves
who are no longer
really Airslaves...
- [Servo] I can't believe
they cut away to me again.
Get the camera off me.
- I am looking for a friend.
- [Joel] The odds
aren't too good.
- I think he's at
the power station.
Together, we will go there
and regain control
of the last city
and New Terra.
(tense orchestral music)
- [Narrator] And so
the new band of rebels
set out on their journey...
- [Servo] Who is that guy?
- [Narrator] Towards
the power station.
- They started at a
landfill outside Manhattan.
- [Narrator] Wastelands.
(tense orchestral music)
♪ Take my hand ♪
- [Joel] I'm a
stranger in paradise.
(tense orchestral music)
- [Servo] I mean, I
guess it's a wasteland
if you don't count that
big city behind you.
- Go to the UN building.
It's filled with
people, behind you.
- [Joel] Maybe they're looking
for the Renaissance festival.
- [Servo] And over here we did
Shakespeare in the slag heap.
It was very nice.
- Follow the yellow brick road.
- [Servo] Follow the
yellow brick road.
- [Narrator] Strange mutants
live in the wastelands.
Posing a threat.
- [Servo] The
shrubbery is alive.
- [Joel] They finally
found the path again.
If I was skeptical, I'd
say that was Central Park.
- Hey, look at this.
- It says this is
not a men's room.
- [Joel] I think it
says no graphics.
- [Servo] Look,
it's the Bangles.
- [Joel] No it's the
roadshow of Cats.
- They're at the Winter Garden.
- [Servo] I'll be
back again and again.
(goofy whirring)
- [Joel] Ah, here's my mark.
- Here's mine.
- [Servo] Hey, that's my mark.
- [Joel] And I'm here.
Everybody stay on camera.
- Don't go for your weapons.
- Who is this woman who
walks through this She Zone
with male scum?
- The woman is with us.
- I speak to the woman.
- I walk with these
men on a mission
to save my father.
- Is that Wendy or Lisa?
- Have you no principles?
- I love my father.
These men have
promised to save him.
- No man is to be trusted.
- Then how can
your tribe survive?
- We use men to breed with us
to create future warrior women.
- [Servo] Cool.
- Then we dispose of them.
- [Servo] Oh.
- Look, he is the last man.
- [Joel] Hey.
It's great.
- He has mated with all of
us who are ready to conceive
and he will now be destroyed.
- And he has nothing
to say about this?
- [Servo] I think he'd
highly recommended it.
- First thing we do
when we find one of you
is to remove your tongue.
Men chatter so.
- You cowardly bitch.
- I would stop if I were you.
- Why, what difference would
the life of one puny man make?
- Perhaps none but there is
a laser pointed at your head.
- Huh?
- How do I know
you're not lying?
- There's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
- What do you want?
- A chance for a fair fight.
- [Narrator] A knife is
placed in the ground.
- [Servo] A voiceover
is placed in the script.
(tense orchestral music)
- They're gonna play mumbly peg?
- [Joel] I'm gonna cut you man,
I'm gonna cut you real good.
- Tear him apart.
- [Joel] You know the
more things change
the more they stay the same?
- [Servo] Yeah like the way
guys and gals get together
and just love.
- Central Park hasn't
really changed, either.
- Rip his flesh.
- David Lee Roth.
- [Woman] Kill him!
- Emmett Kelly.
- [Servo] Puny man, eh?
- By the rules of our
tribe, I belong to you
to do what you will with me.
- All right.
- What do you suggest?
- Kill me because
if I get the chance
I will kill you.
- And why should I kill you?
Your people are like
me, aren't they?
- [Servo] Look at that,
she's stuffing Kleenex,
look at that.
- You can breathe the air.
- The Dark One?
- What a time to get a cold.
- We don't fear him.
He sends transbots to tame us
and we cut them into scrap.
- Your ancestors came
from the wasteland.
- We have no history.
We have always been here.
- So you have a history?
- Others who can exist
here without the device?
- Only Nyla's woman.
We've heard stories of them.
You can help lead us
to the power station.
- I know where it is.
- Then you will take us to it.
- [Joel] Maybe.
- If that is your desire.
But once my debt to you
is paid, I will kill you.
- If you live that long.
- [Servo] Threats,
threats, threats.
- Free the mute, he
will come with us.
- [Nyla] Kai, what
use is he to us?
- [Joel] Hello.
- Maybe none.
Sometimes people can
be help for no reason
other than human charity.
- [Servo] And he can sign.
- They're all useless and crazy.
(Joel coughing)
- I think I have this calender.
- [Narrator] Deep
in the power station
lies the pleasure machine.
- [Servo] All right.
- [Narrator] A reward for those
who loyally serve the Dark One.
(eerie tense music)
(men laughing)
- What?
(eerie tense music)
(upbeat music)
- [Dark One] Valaria.
- Dark One, I--
- The pleasure machine
is to be used as a reward.
Not for habit.
- Yes, Dark One.
- [Dark One] It would
serve you well...
- [Servo] Dog one, boog one.
- I--
- The discussion has ended.
There are other
matters to attend to.
- [Servo] Pretty self indulgent
for someone with a
speech impediment.
- [Dark One] Torque
and the guardbots
bring you a new subject
for interrogation.
- Yes, Dark One.
- [Joel] Is she
wearing a kitchen mat?
- [Crow] Yeah, she
better not go out
in the sun in that outfit.
- Torque, have the man
freed from his bonds.
- James Bond.
- There is no reason for
him to be uncomfortable.
- [Servo] But I kind
of like the chains.
You know, you look familiar.
We're you in Yards of Leather?
- There, isn't that better?
- What, your accent?
- It will benefit all
of us if you cooperate.
Do you understand?
- [Joel] No, none
of us understand.
We don't know
what you're saying.
- Can't understand you.
- You are impervious to
our atmosphere control.
- [Joel] Hey, watch who
you call impervious, lady.
- Your stay with us
could be quite pleasant
if you choose to work with us.
- [Crow] You mean
you'll stop talking?
- On the other hand,
I could introduce you
to worlds of pain
beyond your imagination.
- [Servo] Well, let's just skip
to the worlds of pain, then.
- The choice is yours.
- I have no answers for you.
- A pity.
- [Dark One] I am losing
patience, Valaria.
- Torque, take him
to the crystal.
- [Joel] Torque?
Oh that's what
happened to Peter Tork.
He's doing rubber suit work now.
After The Monkees broke up.
That's interesting.
- I knew that haircut
would come back.
- [Narrator] At the crystal,
Jorn can see that the Dark One
is aware of the
rebel's every move.
- [Servo] There's
that guy again.
- She's your
daughter, isn't she?
- [Joel] Maybe.
- Let go of me, muslin face.
- It would be a pity if
she had to lose her life
because of your silence.
- I have nothing to say.
- [Joel] Uh, except
for what I just said.
- My daughter would
want it that way.
- Then your daughter is a
bigger fool than you are.
- [Servo] She could just like
clear her throat or something.
- Torque, take him to
the room of questions.
- Where is the
room of questions?
- [Joel] Would you stop that?
Don't even start.
Hey, wait for me.
- We will see just how long
he can keep his
secrets to himself.
- [Dark One] Your work is
cut out for you, Valaria.
- [Servo] Your dress
is cut out for you.
- Dark One.
- Stock watt?
- Stock worm?
- Yes, Dark One.
- [Joel] Stock one.
- [Servo] Duck bun, I think.
- [Joel] Beats me.
- See how we fused
this grown cover
to halt the erosion
on this hill?
- There.
- What is it?
- The caverns start here.
- Caverns?
- [Servo] Yes, caverns.
Like between your ears.
- The power station
from underground.
The Dark One has ways of
monitoring our progress
if we continue on the surface.
Come.
- [Joel] I hate
when he does that.
- [Narrator] The mutants
continued to follow the rebels
even as they entered
the underground caverns.
- Hey, it's Shelley Duvall.
(tense music)
- We must be quiet
from here on in.
- Why?
- [Crow] Writer's strike.
- Sewage worms.
- [Crow] Same thing.
- What?
- Sewage worms.
Man eating creatures
from this tribal void.
(Joel chuckling)
- They look like.
- They're blind
but they seek their prey..
- [Joel] Pink socks
with teeth in ''em.
- [Klyton] Humans,
they eat humans.
- [Servo] How 'bout
a show of hands?
(creatures snarling)
- This is their nest.
If we can get to the other side,
we'll be safe.
- Safe?
We'll never make it through.
- What kind of a woman are you?
Have you no fighting spirit?
- Enough.
Let's see how many there are.
(tense music)
- He's carrying a
giant beef stick.
It's Kukla!
- How can we make it through?
- If only we had
some kind of bait
to distract them while the rest
of us slipped through.
- [Joel] Bait, sock bait?
- [Klyton] Will surely
be attacked by the worms.
- [Servo] You can't make
me, you can't make me.
- Kukla, buddy.
- [Joel] Sock broke
my beef stick.
I can't believe it.
Look at this.
He broke my beef stick.
- [Servo] Which one
of them is Ginger
and which is Mary-Ann?
- There's only one way.
- What?
- We chop our way through.
- Yes!
- Ready?
Now.
(goofy tense music)
(shouting)
- Oh, wow.
He got smeared with Rust-Oleum.
- [Servo] What a
time to be caught
without a turtleneck.
- [Joel] I don't think my socks
have ever gotten that bad.
- [Servo] Ew.
- Egg rolls.
- [Klyton] Stop it, worms.
I'm not human.
- [Joel] Hey, Chippa.
- You owe me one, woman.
- So now it's two women?
- I pay my debts quick.
- Now it's back to one woman.
- [Servo] This whole movie
is just socks and violence.
(tense music)
- [Klyton] Just go away.
- [Servo] At least
it's some good work
for the out of work hand models.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Hey, don't
touch my hair.
I worked real hard on that hair.
- You have saved
me a second time.
- [Klyton] Now you
can be his friend.
- So it's two again?
- I owe allegiance to no man.
- [Crow] One.
- No allegiance.
Only your help in leading
us to our destination.
- An oasis lies ahead.
There we can rest.
- And you can get those
little cow cream pitchers.
- [Klyton] What I
need is a tune up.
- [Joel] Dudes, totally
awesome job in there.
Really coming
together as a group.
- [Klyton] Look
at all this water.
It's sure to rust
my microcircuits.
- [All] Shut up.
- [Servo] Hey, this doesn't
look like the brochure.
There was supposed to
be a tennis court here.
- What's down in there?
- Bean fish.
- You don't want to know.
- [Joel] It looks
like a lava lamp.
Oh, it's the Dark One.
- [Dark One] Continue
on their way to us.
- [Servo] The dag wah.
- The rebels,
they're still alive.
They must have
the immunity, too.
- [Dark One] Perhaps.
No matter, is better
that they still live.
- Better?
- [Dark One] Yes.
We can use the girl's
life as (mumbles)
or her death.
- She looks like the
new Lily Munster.
- We have nothing to fear.
- But fear itself.
- Before the might
of our transbots.
- [Dark One] Have you forgotten?
The warrior woman has destroyed
a number of our best units.
- Perhaps, it is
time to send Torque.
- [Dark One] You have made
the right decisions, Valaria.
- [Joel] Then send
Olands and Nesmith, too.
- Has the man revealed
anything to you?
- Just his hernia scar.
- [Torque] His will is strong.
- What power have you used?
- [Torque] We have
taken him twice.
- [Joel] You know, he's great.
You never see his lips move.
- Seven?
He's to be reckoned with.
Take him to nine.
- [Servo] Number
nine, number nine.
Number nine.
(electricity crackling)
(groaning)
- Revive him.
I need him awake.
- [Servo] Revive with Vyvern.
- How can you breathe
the poisoned air?
- Well, I ran a Mexican
restaurant for awhile
than I worked in the
primate house at the zoo.
- Torque, you are to
leave the power station
and intercept the group
that approaches us
and when you reach them,
the first thing you are
to do is kill the girl.
Do you understand?
- [Torque] Yes.
- Do you understand, old man?
- [Servo] Yeah, it's young
girl I don't understand.
- Your daughter
will be destroyed.
You will never see her again.
Now, do you wish
to say anything?
- [Joel] Yeah, do
you know Elmer Fudd?
- Very well.
Torque, go now.
- [Joel] What about
Barbara Walters
or Truman Capote, Daffy Duck?
- You have signed the death
sentence for your own daughter.
- Gee, I know there's an
Easymart around here somewhere.
If we only we could
find the city.
- His wound is infected.
- What can we do?
(growling)
- [Servo] Here's someone
that can help ya.
(shouting)
- I don't think so.
- No!
- [Joel] Grey
stone do something.
Come on, little buddy.
- Use the sharp edge.
(mock grunting)
- [Servo] Hey, I knew
bolos were popular but--
- [Joel] He really
wears it well.
- Damn, cordless thing.
This is going right
back to the store.
- [Joel] Swing easy.
Keep your blade steady.
Your eyes on the head.
- Oh, it's a spare.
Gutter head.
- [Klyton] Get
away, just get away.
- [Servo] Oh man,
can robots puke?
- [Joel] Whoops.
- High fly ball.
- [Joel] Oh there's another one.
Hey, it's a Billy Idol video.
- They're just dancing
with their selves.
- [Klyton] It's a force field.
My only power as a freebot.
- [Joel] Oh, we gotta go.
- [Klyton] Hurry.
- [Servo] Let's get out of here.
- [Joel] Let's us hurry.
- [Klyton] Only 30 seconds.
(dramatic tense music)
(upbeat music)
(laugh track)
- Oh boy, I've got a date
with the McGuffey triplets.
They're contortionists.
The mathematic possibilities
are mind boggling.
(laugh track)
- Hey, Servo.
(applause track)
What's up?
- Got a date with the
McGuffey triplets, Crow.
- Well, better
bring a calculator.
(laugh track)
- Or an abacus.
- Why an abacus?
- One of them is Chinese.
(laugh track)
- If you're dating triplets,
you're gonna have to go
borrow Father O'Leary's van.
- Oh, but he'll never
let me borrow it.
Unless he thinks we're going...
- [Both] To a church meeting.
(laugh track)
(applause track)
- Hi, guys.
Up, up and away.
(laugh track)
What's going on?
- Oh, nothing.
(applause track)
- Really?
- Kinda hanging out.
(applause track)
- It sounds like Cambot's
sitcom simulator's
kinda out of whack.
I better go check.
(laugh track)
(applause track)
My knee.
(laugh track)
Oh man, we gotta--
- Joel, this is awful.
We gotta shut it off somehow.
- Let's do that somehow.
(distorted applause track)
Oh, okay, Cambot, give
us the regular picture.
- Better.
- I guess we've
learned not to toy
with the laws of television.
(alarm blaring)
Oh, we got movie sign.
(all shouting)
(doors whirring)
(dramatic music)
There you go.
- Not too late to
save your daughter.
- Drooder?
- She may be immune.
- Is that what
she said, Drooder?
- But she's not immune
to transbots blaster.
- [Joel] Does she
have like a big piece
of hard candy in her
mouth or something?
- As is mine.
- Meaning what?
- Deeja would rather
both of us die
than have me give
into your demands.
- Do you understand
what you're saying?
- [Servo] Look, sister.
I don't understand
anything you said
for the last half hour.
- I am going to put you through
the tortures of the damned.
When I'm through with you.
- [Crow] Frew?
- You will beg to tell
me what I want to know.
- [Joel] She's
very well groomed.
- Nothing you can do to
me will make me tell you
what you want to hear.
- You're a strong man,
I will grant you that.
No one has ever endured
the room of questions
for as long as you have.
- [Servo] She studied
under Buckwheat, I guess.
- Oh what of Deeja?
Suppose I have
Torque bring her back
to the power station
and put her through
what you have endured.
- You will first have
to catch her, won't you?
- Yes, that is true, isn't it?
- Now, where is that city?
- [Joel] Ah, Queens is
back there behind ya there.
- [Servo] Scarecrow,
Tinman, Lion?
- Hey, who's the
guy in the Huggies?
- [Narrator] Near the
entrance to the power station.
- [Servo] That Depends.
- [Narrator] The rebels
face yet another example.
- [Joel] Oh stop it, come on.
- [Narrator] The
Dark One's cruelty.
- [Joel] Wow, that's the
biggest cardboard cutout ever.
- Wow.
(dramatic music)
Worst matte painting yet.
- [Klyton] These are the winners
of the Airslave battles.
(somber music)
- [Joel] I've seen chickens
hurt worse than that get better.
Give me a slice of that.
- Oh, there's still a
little meat on there, yeah.
- [Servo] In this
compartment of my ring
I fill with a proton
super energy pill.
- [Joel] Thank you, Shoeshine.
You are humble and skeletal.
- [Klyton] It was his father.
- [Joel] Is he
gonna be all right?
- Oh shut up, diaper man.
- [Joel] Hey, it's Jerry Garcia.
(tense music)
- They seem to be upset.
- [All] Huh?
- Do you suppose your daughters
not as strong as
you think she is?
- Deeja can take
care of herself.
And so can I.
- Oh really?
- [Joel] If you were a twee,
what kind of twee would you be?
- Perhaps it is time for
you to see what awaits you.
Behold, the Dark One.
- [Servo] It's a brand new car!
- [Joel] I think you'll like it.
It's got factory air
and all the candy.
Neat huh?
- [Narrator] And so Jorn
was finally face to face
with the being known
as the Dark One.
- Pog wan?
Ravi Shankar.
- [Joel] A being so
hideously expensive,
we couldn't show
it on this film.
(heavy breathing)
- [Servo] Look,
guys, a seal tank.
- Hey, it says
basement to the Alamo.
Come on, guys.
Single file, don't push.
Now, on your right, you'll
see the Alamo rut cellar
and one your left
the Alamo rumpus room
and watch your head there.
Yeah, there you go, Kai.
- [Servo] Aren't you
glad you used Dial?
- [Joel] Don't you wish
all subterraneans did?
- You got underworld wetness.
- We're being watched.
- We have been watched...
- [Servo] Of course
you're being watched.
It's a film, idiot.
- [Klyton] It's true.
It can see all from
the power station.
- Then we have no chance
of taking them by surprise.
- If they we were coming.
- [Joel] They'd of baked a cake.
(tense music)
This kind of looks
like it was filmed
in the furnace room
of a junior high or something.
- Hello, Cleveland.
Rock and roll.
- Let's do it.
- I've never been
this far before.
What lies ahead
is unknown to me.
- [Klyton] We are in...
- What?
- [Klyton] Nothing, nothing.
- Klyton, what
were you gonna say?
- [Klyton] It is called
the vault of beasts.
- Why?
- [Servo] Because hospitality
room was already taken.
- [Klyton] They set
a series of traps
to ensnare those who would
try to invade his domain.
- What kind of traps?
- [Klyton] I don't know.
My microchip board does not
contain that information.
- [Servo] What
good are you then?
- So we're walking
through a live mind field?
- [Klyton] I'm afraid so.
- Well, we can't
just stand here.
Let's go.
- Well, you can just stand here.
I mean, it's possible.
- We move on.
- [Joel] What are they
looking for, anyway?
Clothing?
- Tina is looking for
a support garment.
- [Servo] I hope she
doesn't find one.
- The Nudge has a saggy
diaper that leaks.
- [Narrator] In
the amphitheater,
the Airslaves work to fuel
the Dark One's power supply.
- [Joel] Hey, Johnny,
you heading over to
TJ Smuggler's tonight?
- Are we to remain
slaves forever?
The warrior and the others
have been gone for a day.
We all know that we will
never see them again.
They are dead.
- [Servo] So we can leave?
- Each time we have
tried to escape,
The Dark One has taken
away the air we breathe.
- How did Rosencrantz and
Guildenstern get in this film?
- Korla, all of you listen.
If we stop bringing fuel
to the power station
the Dark One will have
no power to control us.
- Are you mad?
If the Dark One
hears of what you say
we will all die.
- Korla, hear me.
- [Servo] Listen to me,
I was in Godspell once.
- If the warrior and
Deeja still live.
- Hey that guy behind him
got his headphones on wrong.
- Not us.
- So?
- So, we will go
through the motions
of bringing fuel
to the machines.
If the powers of the
Dark One monitor us
they will see us working.
- And?
- And we will bring...
- [Joel] Isn't he
wearing the shirt
that Brando wore in
Streetcar Named Desire?
- Yup.
- [Dark One] What do you see?
- A five dollar globe lamp.
- They are in the
vault of beats.
- [Servo] The walls of Greece?
- [Joel] No, it's not that.
- [Dark One] What
of the Airslaves?
- [Servo] It's not easy
growing the best potatoes
in the world but it's worth it.
- Their work
continues, Dark One.
- [Dark One] Good.
Make sure Torque
tends to our visitor.
- As you command.
- [Joel] You know, they
got a lot of heat loss
coming out of that computer.
A little caulking
would really help.
- Caulking?
(tense music)
- Hey, Cleveland.
- Rock and roll.
- [Joel] Let's do it.
(tense music)
- Hey, crustacean head.
- [Servo] Huh?
(tense dramatic music)
Hey, could you get my lighter
when you're down there?
- Come on, you gold bricker.
Get up, you're not hurt.
Come on, shake it off.
You wuss.
- [Joel] All right, folks.
Back it up, give 'em
some air, everybody.
Come on, he's gonna be okay.
Shows over.
Everybody go home.
Go home.
- [Servo] Hey, guys,
watch that first step,
it's a doozy.
- [Joel] Now, that's
unfortunate skin right there.
- [Servo] He's the craw daddy.
- Hey, he'd be great
with drawn butter.
- [Servo] Or cocktail sauce.
- He's a crust-tafarian.
- [Servo] You know, you
serve him with red red wine.
- [Joel] Okay, okay.
- [Servo] Sorry.
- [Joel] Is that her tail?
- No, she just
played with her stick
until it frayed.
- [Servo] Her dress
looks like something
they cut gaskets out of.
- [Dark One] His will
is powerful, Valaria.
- No one is a match for
your strength, Dark One.
- Dogma?
- [Dark One] There is only
one way for him to know.
- Yes?
- [Dark One] Let
him join with me!
- [Joel] Just wait till this
jet goes over, Dark One.
(low rumbling)
- [Servo] Wait till this
commercial goes over.
- [Joel] Will it go over?
(low rumbling)
- [Servo] Go over great.
- [Joel] Hello, Cleveland.
Rock and roll.
Let's do it, Cleveland.
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] Huh?
- How did the creature die?
- [Klyton] We are not
alone in these tunnels.
- Keep your weapons
at the ready.
- We could be next.
- Not if we remain alert.
Come on.
- [Servo] Aren't they
the kids from Fame?
- They're gonna dance forever.
We're gonna learn how to cry.
- [Servo] Just hope they
don't get to a lunchroom.
- [Joel] Oh, hi ya, crusty.
- Hello, lady face.
- Why would you kill of
one of the inferior beings
instead of the girl?
- [Torque] Their path
away from the body
now leads them to
the beast of the web.
- A Cylon wannabee.
- Torque, your programming is
more advanced than I thought.
- [Joel] Do you think so?
I've really been working on it.
- [Torque] To retrieve the girl?
- No, not now, it is too late.
Whatever information we need
will come from the Dark One.
- [Servo] The dart board?
- He has joined with
the girl's father.
- [Torque] The others?
- If you have lead them
in the right direction
they will no longer
be of concern to us.
- Huh?
- What?
- [Joel] Hey,
wouldn't it be funny
if they ran into master
carpenter, Norm Abram?
- What we're doing here, Bob,
is we got this
little robot problem.
- [Servo] They look like
Heart, the rock group.
- [Joel] Kinda.
The Wilson sisters there.
- [Servo] Oh yeah.
- Why was that mutant killed
and why was it right
in front of us?
- [Klyton] It was a warning.
- a warning?
- [Klyton] A sign that we
should not go any further.
- Ah, you got blemish there.
- [Servo] It's a Robo Shankar.
- [Klyton] The Dark One.
- Dark One?
But why?
- He used to play
with the Beatles.
- Want to stop us.
- [Servo] Robo Shankar?
- Perhaps we knows
we are immune.
- Not all of us.
- Some of us are equity.
- Well I hope not.
Kai is unprotected and so am I.
- Well, the rest of us are fine
and since you are just men,
what difference does it make?
- [Joel] Hey, I think
somebody's forgetting
who's holding the pink
slip, little lady.
- Lowest excuse for a
human I have ever met.
(grunting)
- [Servo] Cat fight.
- There is no time for this.
- Neo!
- You mean duck?
- Help.
- Don't everybody move at once.
- What?
- [Klyton] The beast of the web.
Come, there are only
moments to save her.
(tense music)
- [Servo] The itsy bitsy spider
went up the water spout.
- [Joel] Hello, Marta.
- [Servo] Lancelot.
Lancelot.
- [Joel] Come back,
you dummkopfs.
Come back here.
(tense music)
- Hey, you left your femur.
- Night will fall soon, Roan.
- I know, Korla.
We must continue.
- But they will soon
know at the power station
that we have not
fueled our share...
- [Servo] Hey, posture,
buddy, posture.
- The warrior,
Deeja, and the others
may still live.
- What good can come of that?
- Well, my friend has
Bob Fosse's home number.
- Their might could be
stronger than the Dark One's.
- How?
- The Dark One draws his
energy from our labors.
If we provide him
with no energy,
they just might have a chance.
- A chance?
- Yes.
They are the only hope we have.
- [Joel] Please cross
behind the actors.
Do you mind?
- Well, that settles it.
Let's go to dance class.
- [Servo] And Ramses
said to build a city.
- My favorite food?
Cherry Pez, no
question about it.
- Why should we
wait out the night?
We should strike now.
- The morning will
be soon enough.
- [Klyton] The power station
cannot track us by night.
- All the more reason we
should attack them now.
- Sleep.
They don't know if we
are even still alive.
- He's right.
- [Joel] You know we
could make some s'mores.
- No because he's right.
Besides if we sleep
now for a few hours
we'll be that much alert
for what lies ahead
in the morning.
- You're hopeless.
A man tells you what to do
and you follow his
orders without question.
- I'm following nobody's order.
Neo just makes the most sense.
- Suit yourself.
We wake up dead in the morning,
you know who's to blame.
- [Servo] Funny, we'll be dead.
What a spaz.
- [Joel] There's the Nudge.
Locked, cocked, ready to rock.
- Dude.
- Dog scratch,
No, no, no.
Cat, cat scratch.
I gotta tell somebody.
Cat scratch fever,
this is great.
(low tense music)
- What is it little fella?
Snack, you gotta go walkies?
- [Servo] I can't believe
she's sleeping with an android.
- Ow.
- Gone.
And his brother
called me a coward.
- He's gone on ahead.
- How long ago?
Can you tell?
- No.
- [Klyton] He is headed
towards the power station.
- Come, we must follow.
(tense music)
- Have you freed the
surveillance drone?
- Yes, mistress.
It has been caged
for sometime now.
So, it should be very hungry.
- Go into the tunnels
and prepare...
- [Joel] Do you think they shop
at the same place Mad Max does?
- I don't want it
attacking the girl.
She must get here alive.
- Yes, mistress.
- [Servo] I love it when
he calls me mistress.
- Hey, I had a dream about
a big donut like that.
- [Servo] You know
what that means.
- [Joel] He was hungry?
- [Servo] Sometimes a
donut is just a donut.
- It's the wheel of misfortune.
- [Joel] Looks like the
Pirates of the Caribbean ride
at Disneyland.
- [Servo] It's Rex Smith.
- Boy, I hate coming
to the basement alone.
- [Servo] Not another
extended basement scene.
- Grandma, is it by the peaches?
I'm kind of scared.
- [Joel] There's nothing
there in the dark
that isn't there in the light.
- [Servo] I think I
found grandpa, though.
- [Joel] Part of him.
- [Servo] This
music can't be good.
- Kitty.
Bad kitty.
(man screaming)
(dramatic music)
- How long can we continue this
before we are discovered?
- We must keep on for
as long as we can.
If the Dark One has found
the warrior and the others,
he would of drawn
from the power source
in order to destroy them.
- Since he hasn't?
- Each minute the other survive,
the power of the
Dark One diminishes.
- Let us hope they continue
safely on their way.
- [Joel] And let's keep doing
our stretching exercises.
- I jut hope I find some pants.
- Rock and roll.
- Let's do it.
- Hello, Cleveland.
- Wait.
- Why?
- [Servo] This film is
rated B for basement.
- [Joel] That woman
changes clothes more often
than Mary Tyler Moore.
- [Servo] Lord knows
she's got more pantsuits
than Angie Dickinson.
- I'm impressed.
- [Dark One] They shall
not come any closer.
- Of course not, Dark One.
I have sent Torque to--
- [Dark One] If they do
come any closer, Valaria,
I will be very angry with you.
- Dark one, I assure you.
They are all doomed.
- [Dark One] Expect the girl.
- Of course, master.
She will be brought to you.
- [Joel] Wow, she
must of studied
at the Gabor Institute
of Acting and Attitude.
- [Dark One] And I will
not forgive a mistake.
- You have nothing
to fear, Dark One.
- [Dark One] I know.
But you do.
- [Servo] Uh oh.
Dark One is torqued.
Meanwhile, back in the basement.
- Billy, where are ya, boy?
Billy?
- Hey!
(wet slurping)
- [Joel] Must of been
something he ate.
- Or something that ate him.
- [Servo] Somebody's
been watching Alien.
Oh, don't straddle that thing.
- The boy is dead.
He feels nothing.
(wet crunching)
- Should we get
some Pepto Bismal?
How 'bout a flea collar?
(tense music)
- [Joel] That felt good.
Hey, you cleaned my sword.
Thanks.
- Ew.
- [Servo] Go touch the fence.
- I'm not gonna touch it.
You touch it.
- [Servo] Let's get
Michelle to touch it.
She'll touch anything.
- [Joel] Oh, Scooby.
We gotta get out of here.
- Guardbots, go
to your stations.
- What did she say?
- [Joel] Is she talking to us?
- Huh?
- What?
(alarm blaring)
(upbeat music)
- [Dark One] Valaria,
I'm to believe
that you have failed me?
- No, Dark One.
- [Servo] What she say?
Dar-tag-non?
- Dortmunder.
- Yeah.
- [Dark One] Let this
remind you of what
would be your fate.
(tense music)
- [Joel] She could of
had a really good career
in silent pictures.
- I swear, I will not fail you.
- [Joel] Lovely.
- [Dark One] Very well.
- Wow, you got a cigarette
there, darky baby?
- Torque awaits at the gate.
The girl will be yours,
Dark One, I promise.
- [Dark One] Yes,
she will be mine
or what awaits you
will be far worse
than anything you have
inflicted on any of the others.
- [Crow] Or any of the
effects you've seen so far.
- Power in the gate makes
it impossible to pass.
- [Servo] Well, maybe
try some roughage
or some bran.
- [Klyton] Wait,
I know what to do.
My operational mechanisms
are energized by the same
kind of electrical force.
I can adjust my circuitry
to achieve a matching
level of source input.
The gate's electrification
will not effect me.
- [Joel] Ah, can the
balloon juice, sparky.
Just do something, will ya?
(tense music)
- [Klyton] Almost got it.
- Great, now it's welded shut.
- [Klyton] I feel
like a new freebot.
I will go over.
There should be a release
on the other side to open the--
Malfunction report.
I am but a freebot.
Report malfunction.
Freebot Klyton.
- [Servo] A week before,
that guy was playing Hamlet.
- [Klyton] I will go over.
Malfunction report.
- That, ladies and gentlemen,
is one of the
liberators of Earth.
Pathetic.
- Let me.
- [Klyton] Malfunction report.
I am but a freebot.
Report malfunction.
Freebot like in.
Must repair.
- [Joel] You know, fellas,
it's real sad when it
happens to someone you know.
- [Servo] Yeah,
but sooner or later
it's gonna happen to all of us.
- Tell me about it.
- [Joel] Shouldn't
they get a wallet
under his tongue or something?
- This may take awhile.
- [Servo] It's
too late for that.
Underroos are fun to wear.
(tense music)
Where do you even start
with something like that?
- [Joel] First you cry.
Think you can do a power
sit up, little buddy?
Give him air.
Oh hi ya, crabby.
- Hello, lady face.
- You fool.
You've let them pass the gate.
Do you know what you've done?
- Yeah, I let them
pass the gate.
- [Torque] The iron
wall still stands
between them and
the power station.
- [Dark One] Activate the power
in all sections of the station.
- What is this?
We're operating at only one
fourth percent of capacity.
- [Servo] So it must be
the meter for capacities.
- Dark One, no, we have
watched the Airslaves
work in the amphitheater.
They proceed as always.
- [Dark One] Then
perhaps our visitors
are responsible.
Is this possible?
- Dark One, I will
find out at once.
- [Dark One] Yes, do that.
- Torque, go to
the master monitors
and report to me the
level of energy storage
accumulated from the Airslaves
- [Joel] Crabby do
this, crabby do that.
- [Dark One] Be
careful, Valaria.
The next move that you make
will be the most important
one of your life.
- [Servo] Career decision?
Maybe dental hygiene.
- How do you feel, bucket head?
- [Klyton] I am once
again fully functional.
I am in your debt.
- So what's our next move?
We'll never be able to get
through that wall without--
- [Klyton] Explosives?
- That would be helpful.
- [Klyton] Allow me.
- [Joel] Oh great,
explosive throat cancer.
No thanks.
- Jabbing around in there
and the whole time
you could of gone off
at any moment?
- [Klyton] This
is perfectly safe
without a detonating device.
- How's it work?
- [Klyton] Here, look.
- [Servo] Oh I guess he's
gonna like penny them in there.
Gonna do the shaving
cream under the door gag.
(tense music)
- [Klyton] Don't
just stand there.
Take cover.
- Take cover quick
before the RA gets here.
(explosion)
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] You blew it.
(clearing throat)
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- [Dark One] Your time
runs short, Valaria.
- The guardbots
will contain them.
- [Joel] Huh?
What?
Hey.
Looks like the set from The Wiz.
(group shouting)
- Spinach chin,
you got that way.
- [Dark One] What is to
stop them now, Valaria?
- There are more guardbots.
- [Dark One] And if
they too are vanquished?
- [Servo] Even more guardbots.
- There is one final obstacle
they are about to encounter.
- [Servo] The windmill.
- Now.
- Boy oh boy, if I
weren't a light fixture.
(tense music)
- [Joel] It's the wangosy tango.
You got your Maserati.
- Stop.
- It's a bomb.
Rigged to go off
with any further...
- [Servo] Yeah, it is a bomb.
Maybe you should of
made a different film.
- It will clear the
way for the rest of us.
- Thanks, I needed that.
- There may be some
hope for you yet.
- [Servo] As a Gorgeous
Lady of Wrestling.
- All right, now what do we do?
- I've seen these devices before
at the edge of the wasteland
leading into the last city.
- [Joel] My aunt's got one.
- Listen to me carefully, Kai.
Can you hear me?
- [Servo] Nuh uh.
- From where I stand, I
can't see what you can.
There should be a steel
cylinder in front of you,
near your head.
Is there?
- If that thing goes off,
he'll be playing Vincent.
- Is there a small nod
at the tip of one end?
- [Servo] No knob.
- Slowly, move your
hand up to the bomb
without touching the
wires at your side.
- [Joel] But before you do that.
(tense music)
- Have you got it?
- Now, reach into your
left breast pocket.
- The knob is a
trigger mechanism.
It is attached to the
explosives on the inside
by a very short wire.
Klyton, do you have
cutters in your tool panel?
- [Servo] Well that's a
little personal, isn't it?
(tense music)
- [Joel] Are martinis
good for you guys?
Everybody interested.
- Carefully unscrew the
knob on the cylinder.
When it's loose,
don't pull it away.
Do you understand?
- [Joel] And don't breathe.
- Is it loose?
I'm reaching behind
you with the cutters.
- [Servo] When I'm
done with this,
you will guard my
harem, understand?
(tense music)
- And don't clip your nails.
- Are the cutters
near the cylinder?
Cut it.
Slowly.
Pull the knob away
from the cylinder
just enough to put the
cutters between the knob
and the head of the bomb.
Cut the wire.
Now.
- Poink.
- [Joel] Uh, I
haven't cut it yet.
Just kidding.
Just fake you're
cutting the wires still.
- Larry, our pizzas here.
- What is it?
- [Torque] The energy reservoir.
- Deep dish.
- [Torque] From
the amphitheater.
- [Servo] That guy needs
a Kleenex real bad.
- But we saw them working.
- [Dark One] What
did see, Valaria?
- The Airslaves, they--
- [Dark One] Airslaves?
- [Servo] What?
- [Dark One] The beast of burden
and they somehow
got the best of you.
Valaria, what am
I to do with you?
- Dark One, please.
- [Dark One] Torque, take
her away from my sight.
- No, Dark One, please.
- [Joel] Taking someone out of
an omnipresent being's sight
is pretty tough to do
when you think about it.
- [Servo] But don't.
- I will bring the
girl to you myself
and she will tell you
what you want to know.
(Servo clearing throat)
- [Dark One] One
last chance, Valaria
and then you'll know the
fate that awaits you.
- Thank, you Dark One.
- Diction school.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Oh,
pulsating glass ball
with hair like Sam Donaldson.
Please tell me what to do.
We better get out of here.
- [Crow] Carry me?
- [Joel] No.
- Torque, summon the guardbots.
(doors whirring)
- It was after the apocalypse.
It was after the robots
had taken over the Earth.
There stood a lone,
desperate survivor
in a dark dangerous time.
Crow the hunter
and his animal boy, Geekor.
A lowly human
dressed in the skins
of those lesser
on the food chain
but not by much.
The boldest of them all
was Servo the Blood letter.
Servo the chirping hell beast.
Servo, the defiler
of all that is...
Oh yeah, okay.
So the lonely
triumvirate strode forth
in a search for the morphotic
terror awaiting them
in the dark, evil
power quadrant.
- Uh hey, can we stop at
a Wendy's first, guys?
Geekor here wants a
frosty in a bad way.
- Silence, beaked fool.
You are to mock the
power of the dog wan?
- The blocked wand?
- Bog wan?
What?
- The Dark One, the Dark One.
- Oh, Dark One.
Listen, you know Tom Servo,
I'm not getting too into this.
I feel kinda like King Vitamin
miscast in a Sonny
and Cher video
and besides, are these
real furs or what?
- Yeah, what are we
wearing, roadkill here?
I mean, hey these, these furs
are either cruel or unsanitary,
depending on your point of view.
- Well, it's after the
apocalypse and everything
and well we got the furs
from the dead animals
littering the countryside.
- Ah, roadkill.
See, I told ya, Joel.
We're wearing roadkill.
- Well, that's just great.
Tom Servo is having some kind
of rightwing
conservative fur party
and I think we should
just leave him, Crow.
Let's left mister
narcissist alone here
so he can have his
own party of access.
Let's get out of here.
- Yeah, see ya at the
seal clubbing meeting.
Not.
- He stood proudly.
The bold survivor of the
weak and unwilling race.
You're all my
friends, aren't you?
Tell me your deep dark secrets,
my little furry friends.
We'll roam the countryside
and we'll be one together.
(upbeat music)
(tense music)
- [Joel] Okay, now
I don't want you--
- [Servo] We shall
rule the planet.
- [Joel] I don't want you
wearing this hat anymore.
- [Servo] Hey.
- Hey, that guy had a tough day.
He's off the Murray's
for a Schmidty.
- [Servo] Ever see this one?
We can walk the dog, too.
(metal clanging)
- Boy, if I could fight
like those robots.
Boy, this is what I'd do.
I'd get me some swords
and they wouldn't stand
a chance against me.
- [Joel] Now, how much would
you pay for this robot?
Wait, stop.
There's more.
It slices, it dices.
It makes a great julienne fry.
- [Servo] Hey, not
bad for a crustacean.
Sure, I got my pan flute.
Maybe I should of
brought an oyster knife.
- [Klyton] Let me get.
How did I?
Oh.
- In the future, all robots
will act like Don Knotts.
- [Servo] Hey.
- [Klyton] Oh no.
- [Joel] I saw Darth
Vader do that once.
Uh, uh, you got it.
- [Servo] Cat fight.
- [Joel] Right in the throat.
- See, Dark One,
I kept my promise.
The girl is your.
- [Dark One] You are as
good as your word, Valaria
but your use to me has
still come to an end.
- But, Dark One, I
delivered on my promise.
- [Dark One] Life isn't
always fair, Valaria.
Especially...
- [Joel] Oh, always
get a contract
when you're dealing with
a dark, omnipotent power.
You gotta do that.
- Joel, if we ever
get like these bots,
will you please shut us down?
- [Servo] Just take us out.
- [Joel] She shouldn't be
by that Worthington machine.
You know, those things are known
to have a problem
with their, uh, yeah.
- [Servo] She wasn't
wearing her safety goggles.
- [Joel] That's a problem.
- [Servo] Should of expected it.
(screaming)
- She likes it.
- Dark One, can you hear me?
- [Dark One] Yes, Valaria,
what do you wish to say
before you die?
- You were the one who said it,
I was never really alive.
So what matters to me what
becomes of your followers.
- [Joel] She sounds kinda
like an Obsession commercial.
- The self destruction lever.
- [Servo] Hey
don't turn that up.
Power company says 68, tops.
- The fries are up.
- In five minutes, all of
your domain will be destroyed.
- [Servo] That blast to her face
kinda helped her diction.
- And you and all the others
will cease to exist.
- Well, good as long as
we don't cease to exist.
- Or what?
You will destroy me?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Nothing does.
- [Joel] I don't know
what's gotten into her.
She just doesn't sound like
the malaria I used to know.
- [Servo] Wow, he's, whoa.
- [Joel] Oh, it's the huge Nuge.
(dramatic music)
- That's for R2-D2.
That's for C-3PO.
That's for Julie Newmar
and that's just 'cause I wanna.
What have I done?
- [Joel] Oh man, the huge Nuge.
He's got cat scratch
fever right on his chest.
- [Klyton] No, no!
- Would somebody get
those fries, please?
- Where is my father?
- [Servo] Which father?
That could be anyone.
- [Dark One] He is nearby.
- Take me to him.
- [Dark One] Tell me
what I want to know.
- [Joel] Okay, well
you're kinda cute,
you're kinda pretty,
you drive a big car, too
and when I hold you in my arms,
I never know what to do.
- [Dark One] You and your father
are immune to my powers.
Why?
- I don't know.
- [Dark One] You do and
you will tell me now.
- [Joel] You know, I kinda
miss Earth, you guys.
- [Servo] I can see why.
- Yeah, all that equipment.
- [Joel] Yeah, it's neat.
- Go ahead.
Waste your stupid
energies on each other.
- It's Eartha Kitt.
- What will it matter
in less than a minute
the entire power station
will be destroyed.
- [Torque] What have you done?
- [Joel] What hasn't she done?
- What do you think?
You are finished.
So is the Dark One.
- [Dark One] Torque,
the deactivation lever
is on the far wall.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Hey don't
touch the threads, man.
- [Joel] It's hard
on the fringe.
(dramatic music)
(alarm beeping)
Looks kinda like a solid
gold dance routine.
- [Dark One] Torque, come to
the room of questions at once.
(dramatic music)
Valaria, I thought we
had seen the last of you.
- Dark One, forgive me.
I'm here to serve you.
Please believe me.
- I got no problem with that.
- [Dark One] You
activated the mechanism
that could have
destroyed us all.
- But I can save us all.
Our power is depleted
and it is because
of the traitors
in the work yards
of the amphitheater.
- [Servo] I can't even
guess what she's saying.
- We can force the Airslaves
to begin refueling.
- Come on, Edsel head, speak up.
- And regain our
dominance over them.
- [Dark One] How?
- The girl will tell us.
- Never.
- [Dark One] Why should she?
- When she sees what's
become of her father
and what will become of her.
- Fur?
Did she say fur?
- [Joel] What will
become of fur?
- Hey, my card
opened this teller
and I don't even bank here.
Go figure.
- [Servo] I'm all aquiver
with anticipation.
(dramatic music)
What the?
- [Narrator] All that
remained of Jorn was his head.
The rest of his body
was completely engulfed
by the Dark One.
- [Joel] Looks like something
from One Fish, Two Fish.
- [Servo] I am the eggman.
- Dad, you're a tulip bulb.
- [Joel] Well, at least we
know what McLean Stevenson's
been doing since M*A*S*H.
- Honey, remember my torso?
Well, it's chip dip, now.
- [Servo] Hello, Larry.
- The Dark One has
consumed your father.
Devouring his strength
and (mumbles).
When you are joined with him,
we no longer will
need to ask questions.
- [Joel] Hey, you don't
have to draw me a picture.
Okay, my dad belongs
in the salad bar.
- [Servo] Bet the
inside of his suit
smells like a mushroom
farm at this point.
- [Joel] Well, the
nice thing is her dad
can fly as carry on.
- [Servo] Or carrion.
- Hey, get me, I'm an appetizer.
I'm giving out spores.
- [Servo] I've been wearing
this ridiculous
costume for hours.
I've been cramping
like Cathy Rigby.
(dramatic music)
Stop playing with your food.
- [Joel] Oh please don't
jump on me right now,
I'm feeling kind of vulnerable.
(tense music)
- Crusty's been watching
old episodes of Mannix.
- [Servo] Run away!
(tense music)
She's drunk with power.
- [Joel] She's
drunk with makeup.
- Nah, she's just got
her beer goggles on.
(dramatic music)
- And now it is time
to show the Airslaves
what their treachery
has earned them.
We no longer need them
with the knowledge of
Jorn and his daughter,
we can power the
station from within.
The time has come for
all of them to die.
- [Servo] Oh wait, I'm
on daylight savings.
What am I thinking?
We have an hour still.
(upbeat music)
(coughing)
- They must of unzipped
that avocado suit.
- [Joel] Stay in
character, everyone.
Try to stay on camera.
Oh, she's stone.
- [Servo] Cordless tools.
- [Klyton] Come on.
(screaming)
- [Joel] At least it
worked at the last minute.
- [Servo] They always do,
right when you want
to return ''em.
- [Joel] Oh look at me,
I'm trying to have a fight
and I got Peter Pan
here hopping around.
(dramatic music)
- Uh oh, he's gonna use
the wrapping paper tube.
- [Servo] That's
for putting lemon
and drawn butter on my head.
- [Joel] That guys been the
sand in my shell long enough.
- Let's see.
The human goes through
the hole, around the tank,
and uh, hmm.
There he is.
- [Joel] Just look up.
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Good evening.
- [Joel] Lights are
on but nobody's home.
- [Servo] That's for Mrs. Paul.
That's for Gorton of Gloucester.
That's for Arthur Treacher.
That's for H. Salt.
That's for Filet o' Fish.
- [Joel] Good pose
with the sword.
- You know, if they
put him together
with the avocado man,
they'd make a great
seafood plate.
- Deeja.
I'm as good as dead.
- [Joel] Okay, honey.
Am I a fruit or a vegetable?
- I can't.
I love you.
- If you love me.
- [Servo] He's
Jack the beanstalk.
- This is the only way out.
- Father, please.
- [Joel] You know, I
was gonna help you take
on that big robotic guy
but you seem to be doing
pretty good by yourself, so.
- [Klyton] Take this.
- Here, take my robotic truss.
- [Servo] You know,
underneath all this guac
is a heart of gold.
- You know what to do.
- [Dark One] No, Neo.
We can rule New Terra together.
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
- Take out the pit.
(screaming)
Oh, stir fry.
This is what it sounds
like when bulbs cry.
- [Joel] Thank you,
Neo, for killing my dad.
(soft tense music)
- [Klyton] The Airslaves.
- It's amazing what you can do
just by turning on an egg timer.
- [Joel] Kinda reminds
me of an acting class
I used to have.
(soft tense music)
- [Servo] The Dark One's dead,
avocado man is dead.
(group cheering)
This looks like the locker room
for American Gladiators.
- [Joel] Smells like it.
- Looks like the closing night
cast party of That's Dancing.
(all cheering)
- [Joel] They're
really well groomed
for being at the
end of the world.
- Deeja.
Jorn would of
wanted it this way.
- [Joel] He wanted to be
laid to rest on a hill.
- No.
- [Joel] Not scooped out
for a light lunch, Neo.
- What will you do now?
- Go back to my people,
finish my father's work.
- [Servo] Try to
find a better script.
- No, leave me alone.
- [Crow] Maybe learn how to act.
- Your father was a great man.
- [Joel] And an even
better side dish.
- Well, better
dead than a spread.
- [Servo] What a dip.
(Servo chuckling)
- [Joel] My dads his
own favorite dish.
- [Servo] And she's
my favorite dish.
- Hey.
- Father.
You could still get
a job at Chi-Chis.
You could be the job.
(somber tense music)
- [Narrator] With the
Dark One destroyed.
- [All] Oh, the Dark One.
- [Narrator] Neo
returned to his people
to bring them to the last city.
Together, they would
rebuild New Terra.
- [Servo] So it would
be Newer Terra, then?
- [Joel] Newest Terra.
If not, they might get
their waiter jobs back
or do odd jobs for their
cousin's house painting company
until they got enough
investors for their sequel.
- [Servo] Yeah.
- Oh man, let's pray
it's not a buddy picture.
- [Klyton] I could
take care of you.
- [Servo] He's a
robot, he's a human.
They're detectives.
- Hey, that's not half bad.
It's all bad.
- [Joel] Well, what did you
think of the movie, you guys?
- [Servo] Do you
really want to know?
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Servo] I think it
gave robots a bad name.
- [Joel] I really got upset
by that metallic
panty waist robot.
He really got under my skin.
- [Crow] Yeah, I liked
seeing Nugent, you know,
spread his wings and
try some new things.
- [Joel] Yeah, that was neat.
- [Servo] It's nice
to see him working.
- [Joel] Did you know he's
George Clinton's neighbor?
- [Crow] Who's George Clinton?
- [Joel] Oh, he's
this guy on Earth.
Funkadelic.
He invented funkadelic.
- [Servo] So it's a
rocking neighborhood, then?
- [Joel] Brides of Funkenstein.
Yeah if they have a block party
it's a rocking block party.
- [Servo] The police
have been called.
- [Joel] Yes.
I don't know.
One thing we gotta
do is get a contest
to name that avocado guy.
- [Crow] Oh, good idea.
- [Joel] Have him.
- [Servo] The color
thing was nice.
- [Joel] The color thing?
- [Servo] The fact that
this movie was in color?
- [Joel] Oh yeah.
I mean instead of
looking at black
we're looking at
kind of a burgundy.
- [Servo] It's much better.
- [Joel] Yeah, I like it a lot.
You want to get going?
- [Crow] Yeah, let's uh.
- [Servo] No, I want
to see the key grip.
- [Crow] Let's go
watch some outtakes.
- [Joel] Look at this.
Special visual effects
created by Jeremie Frank
and Bizarrchitecture.
- [Servo] Look, Mr. French.
I didn't know his
first name was Ed.
- [Joel] James Chow.
Chairman's Mao's anagram.
- [Crow] Hey Joel, you ever
look at the floor in here?
Yuck.
- [Joel] It's really a mess,
now that you think about it.
We should have Cam...
Actually I should get
back to fixing Cambot.
- [Servo] Let's go.
- [Joel] All right.
- [Crow] Carry me.
- [Joel] No.
- [Crow] Oh come on.
- [Joel] No I'm not gonna.
Okay, I'll come back for ya.
- [Servo] Your hands are
like the Dark One's, Joel.
- [Joel] All right.
- [Crow] Come on,
carry me, carry me.
- [Joel] Come on, let's go.
Come on, strap your
legs around me.
Okay, let's go.
- [Servo] Hey, Joel,
you gotta come lift me
over this heating grid.
(soft tense music)
(doors whirring)
- Okay, you guys.
It's finally the end
of the experiment
and let's have another look
at that plant guy, again.
Cambot, you wanna fish
out that frame 5236?
There he is up there, guys.
- [Crow] Whoa.
You know, even though
he looks scary, Joel,
I still get a little
hungry just looking at him.
- So we've decided
this guy is too good
to keep to ourselves.
So we're gonna sponsor a name
the plant guy brainstorm.
- Right, it's a
brainstorm, everybody.
So join in.
Send in your name
for the plant guy
and the top 13 will be read
on Mystery Science Theater,
on the Satellite of Love.
- Send your plant guy
brainstorm entries
to Mystery Science
Theater 3000 Fan Club
P.O. Box 5325.
Hopkins, Minnesota, 55343.
- We've come up with a
few starters of our own
to help you name the plant guy.
Number one, Guacamole Wilson.
- [Joel] I've got number two.
Mine is Limbless,
Mucus-Encrusted Avocado Man.
- [Servo] And
number three, Carl.
- So.
Well that finishes up
this week's experiment.
What do you think?
- [Both] What about the letter?
- Oh oh, oh yeah.
Got it right here.
This is from a father/son team.
First is from Donny.
He writes, he's the dad.
"My son and myself would like
to join the MST3K fan club.
That scares the hell out of me
because he's only seven
and I'm 36."
Then later one we've got
some from Bill, the son,
who says, "Hello, Joel.
I'd like to tell
Crow that he's funny
and that I like the
part when he said
he's out of bang bang."
I don't really remember that.
- Maybe he should get
off the sugar cereals.
- Yeah, "and Joel
I'd like to tell you
that when all said nice tag
and Tommy is bubblegum
head without a slot."
- Let's do the nice tag
thing again for him.
On three.
One, two, three.
- [All] Nice tag.
- "PS, all of you are funny.
Thank you, Bill and Donny."
- Thank you, Bill and Donny.
- Thanks.
- How's that, sirs?
- Good job, mister memory.
- I think you should
file this, Larry.
Until next time, skippy drawers.
(soft upbeat music)
(twangy guitar music)
(eerie electronic beeping)
(wind howling)